You know, I woke up this morning and I just decided, you know what I'm not going to engage in anymore is conversations with people who have the United States as the standard.
I just can't do it with y'all.
And this is regardless of race, gender, class, like so many of you only think in the terms of a myopic, American mindset.
You ask questions like, I mean, where would we go besides here?
You say things like, I mean, what are you going to do when America is a third world country?
You know, you you say these things and you think that you are being intellectually challenging and you're not.
You're intellectually challenged.
And I implore you to really take some stock of the fact that you have been indoctrinated with American exceptionalism.
The lie that the United States is a standard of excellence, a standard of morality, a standard of creativity.
And then you see the world and you understand that not only is it not, but that it is actively oppressed and suppressed that everywhere else.
So I am not going to engage any further.
And for the record, all of you all who are like, where would we go?
You would be immigrants.
And I know many of you all have internalized the American lie that immigrants are lazy, that immigrants are moochers or criminals, et cetera.
And it deeply concerns you that you might be seen as that somewhere else.
But I want to just dispel your concerns.
They already look at us like that anyway, everywhere else.
Level it up.
You're damn rude, eh?
Support a real one.